[{
    "question": "In the year 1900 in the U.S. what were the most popular first names given to boy and girl babies?",
    "type": "multi",
    "options": [
        "William and Elizabeth",
        "Joseph and Catherine",
        "John and Mary",
        "George and Anne"
    ],
    "answer": 2
},{
    "question": "When did the Liberty Bell get its name?",
    "type": "multi",
    "options": [
        "when it was made, in 1701",
        "when it rang on July 4, 1776",
        "in the 19th century, when it became a symbol of the abolition of slavery",
        "none of the above"
    ],
    "answer": 2
},{
    "question": "In the Roy Rogers -Dale Evans Museum, you will find Roy and Dales stuffed horses. Roy's horse was named Trigger, which was Dales horse?",
    "type": "multi",
    "options": [
        "Buttermilk",
        "Daisy",
        "Scout",
        "Tulip"
    ],
    "answer": 0
},{
    "question": "TheÂ Daniel Boon museum at the home where he died can best be described how?",
    "type": "multi",
    "options": [
        "a log cabin in Kentucky",
        "a two-story clapboard house in Tennessee",
        "a four-story Georgian-style home in Missouri",
        "a three story brick house in Arkansas"
    ],
    "answer": 2
},{
    "question": "Which of the following items was owned by the fewest U.S. homes in 1990?",
    "type": "multi",
    "options": [
        "when it was made, in 1701",
        "when it rang on July 4, 1776",
        "in the 19th century, when it became a symbol of the abolition of slavery",
        "none of the above"
    ],
    "answer": 1
},{
    "question": "Who holds the record for the most victories in a row on the professional golf tour?",
    "type": "multi",
    "options": [
        "Jack Nicklaus",
        "Arnold Palmer",
        "Byron Nelson",
        "Ben Hogan"
    ],
    "answer": 2
},{
    "question": "Who is third behind Hank Aaron and Babe Ruth in major league career home runs?",
    "type": "multi",
    "options": [
        "Reggie Jackson",
        "Harmon Killebrew",
        "Willie Mays",
        "Frank Robinson"
    ],
    "answer": 2
},{
    "question": "In 1990, in what percentage of U.S. married couples did the wife earn more money than the husband?",
    "type": "multi",
    "options": [
        "8",
        "18",
        "38",
        "58"
    ],
    "answer": 1
},{
    "question": "During the 1980s for six consecutive years what breed of dog was the most popular in the U.S.?",
    "type": "multi",
    "options": [
        "cocker spaniel",
        "German shepherd",
        "Labrador retriever",
        "poodle."
    ],
    "answer": 0
},{
    "question": "In 1985, five percent of U.S. households had telephone answering machines. By 1990 what percentage of homes had answering machines?",
    "type": "multi",
    "options": [
        "10 percent",
        "15 percent",
        "31 percent",
        "51 percent"
    ],
    "answer": 2
},{
    "question": "The first black American pictured on a U.S. postage stamp was who?",
    "type": "multi",
    "options": [
        "Frederick Douglass",
        "Booker T. Washington",
        "Louis Armstrong",
        "Joe Louis"
    ],
    "answer": 3
},{
    "question": "What did the \"D\" in \"D-Day\" stand for?",
    "type": "multi",
    "options": [
        "doom",
        "day",
        "Dwight (Eisenhower)",
        "Dunkirk"
    ],
    "answer": 1
},{
    "question": "The Brownie Box Camera introduced by Eastman Kodak in 1900 had a retail price of what?",
    "type": "multi",
    "options": [
        "$1",
        "$5",
        "$10",
        "$20"
    ],
    "answer": 0
},{
    "question": "Which of these characters turned 40 years old in 1990?",
    "type": "multi",
    "options": [
        "Charlie Brown",
        "Bugs Bunny",
        "Mickey Mouse",
        "Fred Flintstone"
    ],
    "answer": 0
}]